DANIEL DIAS

+1 (289) 885 2240 – 1837 Bonnymede Dr. Mississauga, ON. L5J 1E2 danielnunes@hotmail.com - http://www.dndias.com

SUMMARY

Currently enrolled in the Systems Analyst program, I have 5+ years of experience in the IT field, especially in customer support, networks and Web Development. Fast learner and objective orientated, experienced in teamwork and goals achievement. I have certifications in Cisco networks, ISO 27,002 security and ITILv3 IT processes.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Solid understanding of OSI Model, TCP/IP protocol suite
- Experience in network devices configuration
- SNMP configuration on network devices
- VLAN configuration
- VPN configuration and maintenance
- Windows Server 2008/2012 installation and configuration
- Windows server domain configuration
- DHCP Server Installation and Configuration
- Well-versed in operating systems Windows XP/7/8/10, Linux & MacOS
- Intermediate experience with HTML and CSS
- SEO practices and tools
- Basic knowledge in PHP and JavaScript
- Intermediate knowledge in Java

OTHER SKILLS

- Rapidly adapt to challenges and new situations
- Work well alone or in a group and can act as team leader when needed.
- Experienced in analyze and solve problems
- Able to prioritize task and manage time wisely.
- Capable of handling a crisis and deal with the stress of deadlines.

CERTIFICATION

- CCNA R&S
- ITIL V3 Foundation
- ISO/IEC 20,000 Foundation
- ISO/IEC 27,002 Foundation
- Green IT Citizen

EDUCATION

Sheridan College 2017 - Present

Computer System Technology – Systems Analyst Program

PUC Minas – Belo Horizonte, MG, Brazil

Mar 2015 - Oct 2016

Postgraduate in IT Infrastructure Management

CEUMA University – Sao Luis, MA, Brazil Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems

Jan 2008 - Dec 2011

DANIEL DIAS

+1 (289) 885 2240 – 1837 Bonnymede Dr. Mississauga, ON. L5J 1E2 danielnunes@hotmail.com - http://www.dndias.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Design & SEO (part-time)

Mar 2017 – Present

Digihype Media – Mississauga, ON

- Create website mock-ups
- Website development using WordPress
- WordPress plugins edit
- Website changes to increase SEO
- SEO analysis and reports

Network Analyst

Jun 2015 - Dec 2016

ATIVAS Data Center – Belo Horizonte, MG, Brazil

- Participated in the design and implementation of several network projects, such as:
 - VLAN Segregation
 - Network expansion
 - Network devices replacement
- Installed and configured switches and routers
- · Installed and configures Cisco ASA Firewall
- Designed and implemented network security policies
- Created and configured a backup policy for the network devices
- Update network documentation
- Monitored network performance
- Maintained performance of internal and external networks
- Supported internal and external users

Support Analyst

Dec 2010 – Dec 2014

Dominio Informatics – Sao Luis, MA, Brazil

- Configured and maintained the company servers
- Implemented project to replace more than 300 computers
- Supported more than 400 company users
- Monitored and maintained the internet and external network performance

INTERESTS

- Cooking
- Discover new technology devices, especially gadgets and accessories.
- Movies and TV Shows.
- · Sports, mainly soccer and football.

REFERENCES

Available upon request